adbooth.net 2019-07-09

# Adbooth Display Network

In accordance with the provisions of the Spanish Act 15/1999 of 13 December, on Personal Data Protection and its implementing regulations, the responsible of the website, in compliance with Articles 5 and 6 of Spanish Act 15/1999 of 13 December, on Personal Data Protection, informs all Users that its personal data will be incorporated to an automated file property of ADBOOTH DISPLAY NETWORK, Sole Proprietorship, Spanish company duly incorporated under the laws of Spain, having its Registered Office in Via augusta 2, 43890 Hospitalet de l'infant (Tarragona), with Tax Identity Number B-55.570.303, and registered in the Mercantile Register from Tarragona. 

Users, by ticking the box, expressly and freely accepts that their personal data will be processed by adbooth for the following purposes:

1\. Sending of commercial communications by e-mail advertising, fax, SMS, MMS, social networks or any other electronic or physical method, present or future, which enables commercial communications. The commercial communications shall be related to new products and/or new services offered by adbooth or by the partners that adbooth has signed agreements for commercial purposes. In no event shall adbooth transfer the Users personal data to third parties. In all cases, the commercial communications shall be made directly by adbooth for products and services related to its business. 

2\. Statistical studies.

3\. To process orders, requests or any requirements made by User through any contact method that adbooth makes available to its Users through the website. 

4\. Forward the newsletter from the website: www.adbooth.com. 

adbooth will treat the personal data confidentially and accurately in order to manage the relationships between its affiliates and its customers, as well as the promotion of its business. adbooth informs and expressly guarantees to Users that their personal data will not be transferred, under any circumstances, to third parties. In the event that it will be necessary to transfer the data for any reason, the User must give express consent in written to adbooth. 

All the information requested through the website is mandatory and necessary to provide an optimal service to the User. In case that the User does not provide all the data requested, adbooth do not warrant that the information and services provided fulfils the User needs. 

adbooth guarantees the User to exercises the right of access, rectification, cancellation, and opposition under the terms specified in Spanish Act 15/1999 of 13 December, on Personal Data Protection. Users may exercise their rights by sending a specific request, enclosing a copy of his ID/Passport, to the following address: Via Augusta, 2, 43890 L'Hospitalet de l'Infant (Tarragona), or by sending an email to: support@adbooth.com. Also, the User may unsubscribe from any subscription services provided by clicking the unsubscribe section of all emails sent by adbooth.

adbooth declares that has adopted all the necessary technical and organisational measures to ensure the security and integrity of personal data collected, to prevent loss, alteration and/or access by unauthorised third parties. 

##  USE OF COOKIES AND FILE ACTIVITY 

adbooth on its own name or in name of a third party contracted for measurement web services, may use cookies when a User browse the website. Cookies are files sent to the browser through a web server in order to record the activities of the User, during its navigation. 

Cookies used by the website are only associated with an anonymous User and computer, and do not collect the User's personal data. Using cookies is possible that the web server recognizes the browser used by User in order to make web navigation easier and faster, allowing, for instance, access to Users who have registered previously, direct access to certain areas, services, promotions or competitions reserved exclusively to them without having to register each time. They are also used to measure the audience and traffic parameters, monitor progress and number of entries. User has the possibility to configure its computer to be notified of the receipt of cookies and to prevent its installation. Please, read the instructions and manuals of the browse for more information. For the use of the website is not necessary for the User to allow the installation of cookies when browsing the web, notwithstanding that could be necessary for the User when access to the services that require prior registration or 'login'. The cookies used on this website are temporarily and for the sole purpose of making more efficient the web page navigation. Under no circumstances the cookies are used to collect personal information. 

## IP ADDRESS 

The web site servers can automatically detect the IP address and the domain name used by the User. An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer when it connects to the Internet. All this information is recorded in a file server activity duly recorded that allows the subsequent processing of the data to obtain measurements only statistics that reveal the number of page impressions, number of visits to Web services, the order of visits, the access point, etc.

## SECURITY 

This site uses security information techniques generally accepted by the industry, such as firewalls, access control procedures and cryptographic mechanisms, in order to prevent unauthorized access to personal data. As this, the User agrees that uADBOOTH obtains data for purposes of authentication of the identity for access control. 

All processes that requires the introduction of high personal protected data (healthy, ideology...) will be transmitted by secure communication protocol (https:// ...) and in no event shall third party access to this information transmitted electronically. 

Last modified: April 11, 2012
